foundingfuel.com 2018-06-11

# Founding Fuel

## **ONLINE PRIVACY STATEMENT**

**PLEASE READ THE FOLLOWING CAREFULLY**

GENERAL INFORMATION ABOUT THE POLICY OF THIS WEBSITE IN ITS COLLECTION, PROTECTION, USE AND DISCLOSURE OF THE PERSONAL INFORMATION GATHERED ON THIS SITE.

This website, including all services offered hereon (collectively, the "Site"), is owned and operated by Founding Fuel Publishing Private Limited (FFPPL or "we”). Please note that this Privacy Statement may be revised by FFPPL from time to time, particularly to address changes in our business, the law or technology. If that happens, we will post the revised policy here. Revisions are effective upon posting and your continued use of this Site after the posting will be subject to the changed terms of the revisions.

**LINKS TO OTHER SITES**

Links from this site can take you to third party websites or resources. The information practices of third party websites are not covered by this Privacy Statement or any other policies or terms of this Site. Be sure that you know the terms of use and privacy policy of any linked website before using it.

**WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT**

We collect personally identifiable information about you through:

  * Registration forms on foundingfuel.com or offline

  * Purchase of any our products or services either on the Site or offline

The type of specific Data that we collect may include:

  * Job title
  * Company name

  * Company address, phone number

  * Home address and phone number

  * Mobile telephone number

  * E-mail address

  * Date of birth

  * Any other details if you provide this to us

  * Usage statistics

We may also collect information that we request from you regarding your use of our service or that we collect automatically about your visit to our sites.

The information will be treated confidentially within our company, as we protect other confidential information. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features or use the Site.

**INFORMATION SHARING AND DISCLOSURE**

Except as specifically stated in this statement, our policy is not to share the Personally Identifiable Information collected through this Site with third parties, but we may share this Personally Identifiable Information with other companies and organizations who perform work for us under contract or sell products or services that complement our products and services. We use Personally Identifiable Information for purposes that may include:

  * Providing our users with a personalized service

  * Processing orders, registrations and enquiries

  * Conducting market research surveys

  * Running promotions

  * Providing you with information about products and services we offer (if you agree to receive such information)

  * Sharing your Data with third party organizations who offer products or services which we feel may be of interest to you (if you agree to receive such information)

We also may disclose Personally Identifiable Information (a) in response to a, court order or legal process, to the extent permitted and required by law; (b) to protect user security or the security of other persons, consistent with applicable laws; (c) in connection with a sale, joint venture or other transfer to some or all of FFPPL or the assets of FFPPL; or (d) in order to enforce the Site's Terms of Use.

FFPPL may use a third party service to collect anonymous visitor information like IP addresses, browser types (such as Internet Explorer or Mozilla Firefox), referring pages, pages visited and time spent on a particular site. FFPPL collects this information (1) for statistical analysis of the Site such as web page traffic patterns or usage; (2) to administer our Site and servers; (3) to allow for auditing of our services by some third parties who have that right; and (4) for internal purposes to make marketing decisions.

**PUBLIC POSTINGS**

Users should be reminded that any Personally Identifiable Information that is voluntarily posted by a user to a public area of the foundingfuel.com website (for example, a posting to a bulletin board or chat room) might be collected and used by others. We cannot prevent such uses.

**COOKIES**

FFPPL uses software tags called "cookies" to identify customers when they visit our site. Cookies are used to remember user preferences and maximize performance of our services. The information we collect with cookies is not sold, rented, or shared with any outside parties. Users who disable their Web browser's ability to accept cookies will be able to browse our Website but will not be able to successfully use our Service.

We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. A session ID cookie expires when you close you browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's "help" file. Persistent cookies enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site.

**THIRD PARTY COOKIES:**  We may from time to time engage third parties to track and analyze non-personally identifiable usage and volume statistical information from visitors to our website to help us administer our website and improve its quality. Such third parties may use cookies to help track visitor behavior. Such cookies will not be used to associate individual website visitors to any personally identifiable information. All data collected by such third parties on behalf of FFPPL is used only to provide us with information on site usage and is not shared with any other third parties.

**WEB BEACONS**

Web pages may contain an electronic file called a web beacon, pixel tag or clear gif, among other terms, which allows a web site to count users who have visited that page or to access certain cookies. FFPPL may uses web beacons in the following ways:

FFPPL uses web beacons within the Site to count users and to recognize users by accessing FFPPL cookies. Being able to access FFPPL cookies allows us to personalize your experience when you visit FFPPL web sites that are located both on and off of the foundingfuel.com domain.

**HTML EMAIL**

FFPPL’s practice is to include web beacons in HTML-formatted email messages (messages that include graphics) that FFPPL, or its agents, sends in order to determine which email messages were opened and to note whether a message was acted upon.

**LOG FILES**

FFPPL maintains log files of the traffic that visits our site. We do not link any information gathered in these log files to personally identifying information. Log files are used to manage traffic loads and information technology requirements for providing reliable service. Information collected includes IP addresses and browser types.

**INFORMATION SECURITY**

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.  
All information gathered on the site is stored and maintained in secure facilities that limit access to authorized personnel only.

**RETENTION OF INFORMATION**

FFPPL will keep personal information of its users for as long as they are registered subscribers or users of our products and services, and for a reasonable time thereafter.

**LEGAL DISCLAIMER**

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.

**CHANGES IN THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently.

**CONTACT US**

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should contact FFPPL by emailing support@foundingfuel.com
